A Finding Aid to the Holger Cahill Papers, 1910-1993, bulk 1910-1960, in the Archives of American Art AAA.cahiholg
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence Files, 1922-1979, 1993; Series 2; (Boxes 1-2; 1.5 linear ft.)
  Neumeyer, Alfred (Mills College): 1944
  Nevelson, Louise: 1960
  Newhall, Beaumont: 1941
  New Hampshire: University of New Hampshire: 1939
  Newman, Barnett: 1960
  Newmeyer, S.: [1936]
  New Republic: 1949 (letter from Lloyd Goodrich)
  New York WPA Artists, Inc.: 1977 (including exhibition catalog "Then and Now")
  New Yorker: 1948 and 1952
  New York Herald Tribune: 1948-1952 (3 letters)
  New York Public Library: 1949 (including copies of Index of American Design correspondence dated 1935-1936)
  New York State Historical Association: 1949-1951 (4 letters)
  [New York Times]: 1944
  Neyland, Harry: 1935 (letter to Mrs. Rockefeller with 13 photographs of folk art)
  Norman, Charles: 1960
  Norman, Dorothy (Stieglitz protegee): 1960
  Norman, Geoffrey (Works Projects Administration): 1941 (3 letters)
  North Texas Agricultural College: 1939
  Northrop, F. S. C.: 1947
  Northwest Missouri State Teachers College: 1939
  Norton, Ann: [1960]
  Norwegian Folk Art Museum: 1949 (2 letters)
  Odegaard, Charles E. (American Council of Learned Societies): 1949 (3 letters)
  O'Hara, Frank (poet and art critic): 1960
  Okada, Kimi and Keryo: 1960
  Olmsted, Harold S.: 1954
  Olsen, Catharine M.: 1941, undated (3 letters)
  O'Neill, John P. (Historic American Buildings Survey, Department of the Interior): 1936 (5 letters)
  Organ, Violet: 1949
  Ormsbee, Thomas H. (editor, American Collector): 1936 (letter to Ruth Reeves)
  Osborn, Elodie: 1960
  O'Steen, Alton (Alabama Dept. of Education): 1943
  Pach, Walter: 1939 (photograph of letter to Friends of the FAP)
  Parker, Margaret: [1960]
  Parker, Thomas C. (Federal Art Proj.): 1936-1940 (14 letters)
  Parkinson, Eliza (Museum of Modern Art trustee): 1960
  Parr, Russell C.: 1936
  Parsons, Betty: 1960
  Pedlar, Sylvia: 1960
  Pedro, Luis Martinez: 1947
  Peixotto, Ernest: 1936
  P.E.N. Club, The: 1948
  People's Art Center Association, St. Louis: 1952 (5 letters)
  Pereira, Irene Rice and George Reavey: 1950-1953 (21 letters)
  Perry, Beatrice (Gres Gallery): 1960
  Philadelphia Museum of Art: 1950
  Pickens, Alton: 1955
  Pietan, Norman: 1948 and [1949]
  Pilgrim Society: 1949 (2 letters)
  Pollack, Peter: 1960
  Pollak, Frances M. (WPA): 1936-1949 (7 letters)
  Pollet, Elizabeth (widow of artist Joseph Pollet): [1960]
  Pollock, Jackson: 1952 (photocopy)
  Price, R. Moore: 1945
  Public Use of Arts Committee: 1939
  Purcell, Ralph: 1949 (4 letters)
  Pyle, Edward Frederick: 1939
  Ramsay, John: mentioned in memo dated Mar 31, 1936
  Reeves, Ruth: 1936-1949 (55 letters including field reports)letters)
  Reines, Harriet: 1938
  Reinhart, Ad: 1952-1959 (3 letters)
  Reynal and Hitchcock, Inc.: 1937
  Richardson, E. P. (Detroit Institute of Arts; Archives of American Art): 1951-1960 (7 letters)
  Riefstahl, Elizabeth: 1936
  Ritchie, Andrew C.: 1944 (2 letters)
  Rivers, Larry: 1960
  Robinson, Boardman: 1936 and 1960
  Rockefeller Center, Inc.: 1934 (contract for the First Municipal Art Exhibition)
  Rockefeller Foundation: 1949
  Rockefeller, David: 1960
  Rockefeller, John D., Jr., and Abby A.: 1934-1940 (4 letters)
  Rockefeller, John III, and Blanchette: 1951-1960 (3 letters)
  Rockefeller, Nelson A.: 1934-1960 (6 letters)
  Rockefeller, Peggy: 1960
  Roesen, Severin: mentioned in letter dated Mar 02, 1938
  Roosevelt, Franklin D.: 1936-1940 (3 letters)
  Rosenbaum, Belle ( New York Herald Tribune): 1949-1960 (4 letters)
  Rosenwald, Janet: 1937 and 1960
  Rothko, Mark: 1960
  Rourke, Constance: 1935-1938 (57 letters)
  Rowan, Edward B. (Treasury Department, Section of Painting and Sculpture): 1936-1943 (5 letters)
  Rubenstein, Erica B.: 1945 (3 letters)
  Rubenstein, Sarah (Museum of Modern Art): 1960
  Russell, Morgan: 1950-1951 (2 letters)
  St. Petersburg Federal Galleries: 1939
  Sandoz, Mari (writer): 1960
  Sawitzky, William (painting researcher): 1935 (2 letters)
  Sawyer, Wilda A.: 1942
  Saxon, Lyle: 1943
  Schaefer, Bertha: [1960]
  Scharf, Bill: [1960]
  Scheidt, Melvin E. (War Relocation Authority): 1943
  Schmidt, Katherine: 1944 and 1960
  Schnitzer, Robert C.: 1949
  Schwabacher, Ethel: 1960 (2 letters)
  Scott, Cecil: 1960 (2 letters)
  Scott, Phyllis C.: 1936-1937 (2 letters)
  Scull, Ethel and Bob (art collectors): [1960]
  Seckar, Alvena V.: 1946
  Seeger, Charles: 1936
  Selz, Peter and Thalia: 1960
  Shaw, Charles: 1960
  Simms, Agnes (artist): 1960
  Siporin, Mitchell: 1943-1960 (4 letters)
  Sloan, Helen (Mrs. John Sloan): 1951 and 1960
  Sloane, William: 1945
  Smedley, Agnes: 1947 (letter from Ernestine Evans)
  Smith College: 1944-1950 (6 letters)
  Smith, Ferdinand: 1952
  Smith, Geneva: 1942 (memo from Frank J. Follmer)
  Smith, Gordon M. (Index of American Design): 1936-1937 (8 letters)
  Smith, Holly and Sam: [1960]
  Smith, Joseph Lindon: mentioned in letter dated Mar 28, 1950
  Smith, Laura: 1938-1939 (5 letters)
  Smith, Louise: 1960
  Smith, Margery Hoffman (FAP, Oregon): 1938
  Soby, James Thrall: 1948-1960 (5 letters)
  Soderblom, Nathan: 1922 (in Swedish)
  Solomon, Saul (Cahill's doctor): 1960
  Soyer, Moses: 1944 (letter to the Editor)
  Spark, Mrs. Victor: 1960
  Speck, Walter: 1939 (2 letters)
  Spencer, Betty (Niles Spencer's first wife): 1960
  Spencer, Catherine (Mrs. Niles Spencer): 1952-1960 (8 letters)
  Stamos, Theodoros: 1960
  Standards: National Bureau of Standards: 1941
  State: Department of State: 1939 (3 letters)
  Stavenitz, Alexander: 1937
  Steegmuller, Francis: 1960
  Stella, Joseph: 1936 (2 letters)
  Sterner, Albert: 1935
  Stieglitz, Alfred: 1932 and 1934
  Stier, W. (Project Review Section): 1941
  Still, Clyfford: 1953-1956 (4 letters)
  Stix, Hugh: 1960
  Stock, Joseph (artist): mentioned in letters dated 1932 and 1933
  Stout, Rex: 1944
  Strickland, Sidney: 1949 (2 letters)
  Studio Publications, Inc.: 1951
  Sunami, Soichi: 1960
  Swasey, Jeannette: [1935]
  Sweeney, Jim: [1960]
  Tabak, Maynatalie (colleague of Jackson Pollock): [1960]
  Taub, Alex: 1942 (memo from Buckminster Fuller)
  Taylor, Francis Henry: 1939 and 1952
  Taylor, Miss: 1936
  Thomas, Yvonne (artist): 1960
  Thomley, John: 1949
  Thoms, Mr.: 1936 (letter from Matthew Daly)
  Thorgurson, Nina: [1960]
  Tobey, Mark: 1954 and 1960
  Tobey, Judith (Resettlement Administration): 1936
  Townsend, Gertrude: [1937]
  Townsend, Mr.: 1938
  Tranum, Carl K.: 1949 (2 letters)
  Triggs, Clayton E.: 1940 (4 letters)
  Turner, Katherine: [1935]
  Tworkov, Jack and Wally: 1960
  Uht, Charles (photographer of Nelson Rockefeller's collection): 1960
  United American Artists: 1940
  Valentin, Curt: 1954
  Valentine, Chapin: 1932
  Valentiner, W. R. (Detroit Institute of Arts): 1933
  Varian, Dorothy: 1960
  Viviano, Catherine (art dealer): [1960]
  Volkmer, Jean (Museum of Modern Art conservator): [1960]
  von Wiegand, Charmion (artist): 1960
  Walker, Hudson D.: 1960
  Walley, Jano and John: 1949 and 1960
  Ward: 1925 and 1960 (3 letters)
  War Department: 1938-1941 (5 letters)
  Warren, William (FAP, Connecticut): 1937
  Wasey, Jane: 1960
  Washburn College: 1939
  Washburn, Gordon (Albright Art Gallery): 1960
  Washington: The State College of Washington: 1939
  Watrous, Harry W.: 1936
  Watson, Forbes: 1949
  Webb, Aileen (American Handicraft Council): 1938 (4 letters)
  Weber, Max: 1922-1960 (6 letters)
  Weisenborn, Fritzi (Mrs. Rudolph Weisenborn): 1950
  Wendt, Gerald (Time, Inc.): 1944 (2 letters)
  Weston, Edward: 1936
  Wharton, Frances L.: 1935 (2 letters)
  Wheeler, Monroe (Museum of Modern Art): 1960
  White, Francis Robert: 1944
  White, Jim: 1960
  Whitelaw, Robert N. S.: 1960
  Whitney Museum of American Art: 1949 and 1979
  Whyte, James C.: 1942
  Wilfred, Thomas: 1960
  Williams, Aubrey (WPA): 1936
  Williamsburg Restoration, Incorporated: 1935 (4 letters)
  Winchester, Alice ( Antiques Magazine): 1950-1951 (6 letters)
  Winser, Beatrice: 1924-1944 (6 letters)
  Winter, Anna K. (antiques dealer): 1935
  Wisconsin: State Historical Society of Wisconsin: 1939
  Woodstock Artists Association: 1960
  Woodward, Ellen S.: 1936-1938 (3 letters)
  Worcester, Wakefield (architect): 1936
  Wright, Russell (industrial designer): [1960]
  Wyn: A. A. Wyn, Inc.: 1951
  Youngerman, Jack: 1960
  Zegri, Armando (Galeria Sudamericana): 1960
  Zimmerman, Fred and Dorothy: [1960]
  Zorach, William: 1936-1960 (3 letters)
  - Correspondence, undated (Reel 5285, Frame 0673-0704)
  - Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Reel 5285, Frame 0706-0717)
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Reel 5285, Frame 0718-0728)
  - Correspondence, 1930-1931 (Reel 5285, Frame 0729-0749)
  - Correspondence, 1932-1933 (Reel 5285, Frame 0751-0770)
  - Correspondence, 1934 (Reel 5285, Frame 0772-0790)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1935 (Reel 5285, Frame 0792-0836)
  - Correspondence, March-June 1935 (Reel 5285, Frame 0838-0882)
  - Correspondence, July-December 1935 (Reel 5285, Frame 0884-0914)
  - Correspondence, January 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 0916-0936)
  - Correspondence, February 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 0938-1003)
  - Correspondence, March 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1005-1054)
  - Correspondence, April 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1056-1089)
  - Correspondence, May 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1090-1103)
  - Correspondence, June 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1104-1131)
  - Correspondence, July 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1132-1153)
  - Correspondence, August 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1155-1205)
  - Correspondence, September 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1206-1220)
  - Correspondence, October 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1221-1242)
  - Correspondence, November 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1243-1282)
  - Correspondence, December 1936 (Reel 5285, Frame 1283-1303)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1937 (Reel 5285, Frame 1304-1341)
  - Correspondence, July 1937 (Reel 5285, Frame 1342-1389)
  - Correspondence, August 1-13, 1937 (Reel 5285, Frame 1390-1420)
  - Correspondence, August 14-31, 1937 (Reel 5285, Frame 1421-1458)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1937 (Reel 5285, Frame 1459-1474)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1937 (Reel 5285, Frame 1475-1501)
  - Correspondence, January-August 1938 (Reel 5285, Frame 1502-1534)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1938 (Reel 5286, Frame 0003-0045)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1939 (Reel 5286, Frame 0046-0068)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1939 (Reel 5286, Frame 0069-0089)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1939 (Reel 5286, Frame 0091-0113)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1939 (Reel 5286, Frame 0114-0149)
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 23)
  - Correspondence, January-March, 1940 (Reel 5286, Frame 0150-0220)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1940 (Reel 5286, Frame 0221-0255)
  - Correspondence, July-December 1940 (Reel 5286, Frame 0256-0308)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1941 (Reel 5286, Frame 0309-0360)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1941 (Reel 5286, Frame 0361-0407)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1941 (Reel 5286, Frame 0408-0445)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1941 (Reel 5286, Frame 0446-0471)
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Reel 1105, Frame 0024-0046)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1942 (Reel 5286, Frame 0472-0511)
  - Correspondence, July-December 1942 (Reel 5286, Frame 0512-0530)
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Reel 1105, Frame 0047-0064)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1943 (Reel 5286, Frame 0531-0576)
  - Correspondence March-April 1943 (Reel 5286, Frame 0578-0607)
  - Correspondence May-December 1943 (Reel 5286, Frame 0608-0649)
  - Correspondence January-May 1944 (Reel 5286, Frame 0650-0684)
  - Correspondence June-December 1944 (Reel 5286, Frame 0685-0718)
  - Correspondence 1945 (Reel 5286, Frame 0719-0772)
  - Correspondence 1946 (Reel 5286, Frame 0773-0822)
  - Correspondence 1947 (Reel 5286, Frame 0823-0836)
  - Correspondence, January-May 1948 (Reel 5286, Frame 0837-0888)
  - Correspondence, June-December 1948 (Reel 5286, Frame 0889-0923)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 0924-0950)
  - Correspondence, March 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 0951-0984)
  - Correspondence, April 1-12, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 0985-1021)
  - Correspondence, April 13-28, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1022-1039)
  - Correspondence, April 29-30, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1040-1079)
  - Correspondence, May 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1080-1105)
  - Correspondence, June 1-9, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1106-1146)
  - Correspondence, June 10-21, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1147-1179)
  - Correspondence, June 22-30, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1180-1199)
  - Correspondence, July 1-14, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1200-1223)
  - Correspondence, July 15-31, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1224-1240)
  - Correspondence, August 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1241-1247)
  - Correspondence, September 1-12, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1248-1286)
  - Correspondence, September 14, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1287-1347)
  - Correspondence, September 15-30, 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1348-1364)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1949 (Reel 5286, Frame 1365-1392)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1950 (Reel 5286, Frame 1393-1417)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1950 (Reel 5286, Frame 1418-1442)
  - Correspondence, July-October 1950 (Reel 5286, Frame 1443-1484)
  - Correspondence, November 1950 (Reel 5286, Frame 1486-1513)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1950 (Reel 5287, Frame 0003-0024)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1951 (Reel 5287, Frame 0025-0059)
  - Correspondence, April-August 1951 (Reel 5287, Frame 0060-0091)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1951 (Reel 5287, Frame 0092-0119)
  - Correspondence, January-May 1952 (Reel 5287, Frame 0120-0154)
  - Correspondence, June-August 1952 (Reel 5287, Frame 0155-0186)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1952 (Reel 5287, Frame 0187-0202)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1953 (Reel 5287, Frame 0203-0218)
  - Correspondence, July-December 1953 (Reel 5287, Frame 0219-0250)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Reel 5287, Frame 0251-0286)
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Reel 5287, Frame 0287-0332)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Reel 5287, Frame 0333-0359)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Reel 5287, Frame 0360-0401)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0402-0406)
  - Correspondence, July 1960; (3 folders) (Reel 5287, Frame 0407-0516)
  - Correspondence, July 7-8, 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0517-0548)
  - Correspondence, July 9-10, 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0550-0614)
  - Correspondence, July 11, 1960; (2 folders) (Reel 5287, Frame 0615-0662)
  - Correspondence, July 12, 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0663-0688)
  - Correspondence, July 13-14, 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0689-0727)
  - Correspondence, July 15-18, 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0728-0767)
  - Correspondence, July 19-24, 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0768-0803)
  - Correspondence, July 25-31, 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0804-0829)
  - Correspondence, August 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0831-0880)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1960 (Reel 5287, Frame 0881-0925)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1972 (Reel 5287, Frame 0927-0932)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Reel 5287, Frame 0933-1006)
  - Correspondence, 1979, 1993 (Reel 5287, Frame 1008-1014)
- Works Progress Administration Federal Art Project, 1934-1970; Series 3; (Boxes 2-14, 18, MMs009; 10.75 linear ft.)
  This series documents Cahill's directorship of the WPA FAP from 1935 to 1943 and provides fairly comprehensive coverage of the development, operation, problems and accomplishments of FAP projects at the national and state level. Records include correspondence and memoranda, national and state reports, financial records, meeting minutes, exhibition files, printed material, scrapbooks and photographs and date from 1934 to 1970 with the bulk of the material dating from 1935 to 1943.
  Arrangement note
  The series is arranged into fourteen subseries:
  3.1: General Subjects, circa 1934-1943, 1953
  3.2: Artist Files, 1935-1943
  3.3: Administration of the National WPA/FAP, 1935-1942
  3.4: Administration of the State WPA/FAP, 1935-1943
  3.5: Meeting Minutes and Transcripts, 1936-1941
  3.6: Allocations, 1935-1943, 1970
  3.7: Community Art Centers, 1934-1946
  3.8: FAP Divisions, 1935-1940
  3.9: Index of American Design, 1936-1947
  3.10: Exhibitions, 1935-1942
  3.11: Other New Deal Art Projects, 1935-1942
  3.12: Publicity and Printed Material, 1934-1944, 1961
  3.13: Scrapbooks, 1936-1939
  3.14: Photographs, circa 1935-1948
  - General Subjects, circa 1934-1943, 1953; 3.1
    This subseries contains general records of the FAP including correspondence and memoranda, information on administrators, advisory committee records, employment statistics, manuals and reports.
    Records relating to administrators include biographical sketches and/or photographs of the following FAP administrators: Donald Bear, Thaddeus Clapp, D. S. Defenbacher, Audrey McMahon, Eric Mose, Concetta Scaravaglione, Alexander Stavenitz, and George Thorp. The records include photos of McMahon, Mose, Scaravaglione, Stavenitz, and Thorp.
    Advisory committe records include lists of committee members for the Federal Music Project, the Federal Theatre Project, and the Federal Art Project; correspondence related to the selection of members for the Fine and Applied Arts Committee of the FAP; and information (such as names, addresses and occupations) concerning members of FAP advisory committees organized by state.
    General files include reports on various aspects of the FAP and general program operations and accomplishments, program descriptions and summaries, procedural documents and administrative forms. These are followed by lists of FAP projects, a notebook documenting FAP activities in the southern states and a report on the FAP's activities to 1939.
    Also found here are records relating to support and criticism of the FAP, the war effort and "negro art" including memoranda, reports, a typescript of a speech by Thomas C. Parker, press releases and printed material.
    - Administrators, Lists of, circa 1935-1936 (Reel 5287, Frame 1132-1142)
    - Administrators, Photographs and Biographical Sketches, circa 1935-1936 (Reel 5287, Frame 1143-1171)
    - Advisory Committees, circa 1935 (Reel 1105, Frame 0366-0382)
    - Advisory Committees Correspondence, 1935 (Reel 1105, Frame 0383-0408)
    - Advisory Committees, Alabama, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0409-0414)
    - Advisory Committees, California, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0415-0431)
    - Advisory Committees, Colorado, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0432-0434)
    - Advisory Committees, Connecticut, 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 435)
    - Advisory Committees, Delaware, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0436-0438)
    - Advisory Committees, District of Columbia, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0439-0441)
    - Advisory Committees, Florida, 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0442-0444)
    - Advisory Committees, Illinois, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0445-0453)
    - Advisory Committees, Iowa, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0454-0464)
    - Advisory Committees, Louisiana, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0465-0468)
    - Advisory Committees, Maine, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0469-0471)
    - Advisory Committees, Maryland, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0476-0481)
    - Advisory Committees, Massachusetts, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0472-0475)
    - Advisory Committees, Michigan, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0482-0492)
    - Advisory Committees, Minnesota, 1939 (Reel 1105, Frame 493)
    - Advisory Committees, Missouri, 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 494)
    - Advisory Committees, Montana, 1939 (Reel 1105, Frame 495)
    - Advisory Committees, New Hampshire, 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 496)
    - Advisory Committees, New Jersey, 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0497-0499)
    - Advisory Committees, New York, 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0500-0501)
    - Advisory Committees, North Carolina, 1939 (Reel 1105, Frame 502)
    - Advisory Committees, Ohio, 1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 503)
    - Advisory Committees, Oklahoma, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 504)
    - Advisory Committees, Oregon, 1939 (Reel 1105, Frame 0505-0509)
    - Advisory Committees, Pennsylvania, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0510-0515)
    - Advisory Committees, Rhode Island, circa 1939-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0516-0517)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, circa 1935 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0399-0400)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1935-1936; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0374-0398)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1935-1936; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0682-0728)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1937 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0417-0430)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0729-0733)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1939 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0431-0479)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0734-0740)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0748-0754)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940; (1 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0480-0488)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940; (2 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0741-0743)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940; (3 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0746-0747)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0744-0745)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0755-0766)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0489-0493)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1943 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0767-0789)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, circa 1943 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0798-0803)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1953 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0790-0797)
    - Draft Operating Manual of Museum Services and Education Aids, circa 1935-1940 (Reel 1105, Frame 0581-0615)
    - Employment Figures, 1935-1936, undated (Reel 1107, Frame 0383-0422)
    - Employment Figures, January-March 1936 (Reel 1107, Frame 0423-0453)
    - Employment Figures, April-December 1936 (Reel 1107, Frame 0454-0480)
    - Employment Figures, 1937-1942 (Reel 1107, Frame 0481-0507)
    - Employment Figures, 1942 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 1031-1032)
    - General Files, undated; (1 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 340)
    - General Files, undated; (2 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0558-0559)
    - General Files, undated; (3 of 3) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0665-0667)
    - General Files, circa 1934-1935 (Reel 5288, Frame 0093-0245)
    - General Files, circa 1935; (1 of 2) (Reel 1105, Frame 0282-0292)
    - General Files, circa 1935; (2 of 2) (Reel 5288, Frame 0247-0400)
    - General Files, circa 1936 (Reel 5288, Frame 0401-0574)
    - General Files, 1936; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0401-0416)
    - General Files, 1936; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0822-0853)
    - General Files, circa 1937; (1 of 2) (Reel 5288, Frame 0575-0804)
    - General Files, circa 1937; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0569-0601)
    - General Files, circa 1938 (Reel 5288, Frame 0805-1117)
    - General Files, circa 1939 (Reel 5288, Frame 1118-1243)
    - General Files, 1939; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0606-0615)
    - General Files, 1939; (2 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0873-0889)
    - General Files, circa 1940 (Reel 5288, Frame 1244-1520)
    - General Files, 1940 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0657-0664)
    - General Files, circa 1941 (Reel 5289, Frame 0004-0227)
    - General Files, circa 1935-1942 (Reel 1105, Frame 0557-0580)
    - General Files, circa 1942 (Reel 5289, Frame 0229-0260)
    - General Files, 1942; (1 of 2) (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0645-0654)
    - General Files, 1942; (2 of 2) (Reel 1105, Frame 0542-0552)
    - General Files, circa 1942-1943 (Reel NDA 15, Frame 0890-0977)
    - General Files, circa 1943 (Reel 5289, Frame 0261-0362)
    - Lists of Projects, 1942 (Reel 5287, Frame 1120-1128)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 1940-1942 (Reel 1109, Frame 1023-1065)
    - Notebook, FAP Region 3, Southern, 1935 (Reel 5287, Frame 1405-1493)